Toast to the knights that left our voices sore Arm in arm with mischief in our eyes
Every song a bond, our spirits high Stomping feet, we own this fight
Hearts ablaze, we unite every sound Journey on from dusk till dawn
We're bound Raise your pints up, friends of mine
Yeah, flow, you're always by my side We're not gonna fret, not one small doubt
Every tale's a crack with you about We're gonna shred some strings, stage a light
Screaming anthems through the night We are now
Now we march to the beat of our drum Thrashing harder, come what may come
We're the kings of this emerald town With every uproar, we claim the crown
Leaning in as the crowd roars loud Flow and I in this raucous crowd
Through the tavern doors, our legend grows Stout hearts entwine like Celtic knots, who knows?
Every shanty, every cheer we compose Flow, you're the maids who always toast